(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます
部屋を明るくし画面から十分離れてご視聴ください
*This broadcast contains scenes with intense flashing lights.
Please watch in a bright room and keep a safe distance from the screen.
START!!
もう 振り向かず 歩いてゆけるさ
I can walk on without looking back now
いつか また逢う その日まで
Until the day we meet again
君の 夢がきっと 叶うように
I'm praying to that star
あの星に願っているよ
That your dreams will surely come true
Distance -Special Full Version-
作詞・作曲：Daito Music
Lyrics & Composition: Daito Music
もうすぐ 逢えなくなる 君の突然の言葉
Soon we won't be able to meet, your sudden words
何も考えられず ただうつむいた
I couldn't think of anything, I just looked down
夜も眠れずに 涙をこらえて
Unable to sleep at night, holding back tears
ずっと答えを探してた
I was searching for an answer all along
だけど本当に君が好きだから
But because I truly love you
信じ続けたい
I want to keep believing
もう 振り向かず 歩いてゆけるさ
I can walk on without looking back now
いつか また逢う その日まで
Until the day we meet again
君の 夢がきっと 叶うように
I'm praying to that star
あの星に願っているよ
That your dreams will surely come true
どんなに遠く 2人離れても
No matter how far apart we are
ずっと君を想っている
I'll always be thinking of you
この寂しさを 乗り越えられたら
If I can overcome this loneliness
きっと笑顔でまた逢える
I'm sure we can meet again with a smile
やがて時は流れて 何気ない毎日
Time passed, and the ordinary days
ただ穏やかな日々が 流れていった
Just peacefully flowed by
遠く離れても 2人の写真は
Even if we're far apart, the photo of us two
いつも笑顔でいてくれる
Always stays smiling
見知らぬ場所で君が輝くから
Because you're shining in an unfamiliar place
Distance ~Special Full Version~
もう振り向かず歩いて行けるさ
I can keep walking without looking back now
いつかまた逢うその日まで
Until the day we meet again
君の夢がきっと叶うように
So that your dreams will surely come true
あの星に願っているよ
I'm wishing upon that star
どんなに遠くふたり離れても
No matter how far apart we are
ずっと君を想っている
I'll always be thinking of you
この寂しさを乗り越えられたら
Once we've overcome this loneliness
きっと笑顔でまた逢える
We can surely meet again with a smile
また逢える...
Meet again...
ちょっとマイク取られちゃったぺこだけど、まあいっか！
I got my mic taken away, but oh well!
みんな！ぺこらの生誕ライブに来てくれてありぺこー！
Everyone! Thanks for coming to Pekora's birthday live!
本日のハッシュタグは #兎田ぺこら生誕祭2025、たくさん呟いてね！
Today's hashtag is #PekoraBirthday2025. Please tweet a lot!
というわけで、もう一曲目の曲からなんとなく
So, since the first song...
あれ？今回のライブのテーマ、あれなのかな？って思った人もいると思いますが
...some of you might be thinking, "Wait, is that the theme of this live?"
まずはステージを見てください！
But first, take a look at the stage!
たらー！すごいの！なんだこれは！これはなんなんだー！
Ta-da! It's amazing! What is this?! What in the world is this?!
ということでね、まあこの後ちょっとゲストパートもあるぺこなんですけども
So, there's going to be a guest segment later.
まあみんなが知ってる曲だったりとか
I'll be performing songs everyone knows...
もしかしたら知らない曲もあるかと思いますが
...and maybe some you don't.
めちゃめちゃね、楽しい曲もあるぺこですので
There are some really fun songs as well...
お楽しみに！
...so look forward to it!
というわけで、じゃあ早速、行ってきやしょう！
All right then, let's get right into it!
ではではー！
Here we go!
舞台
Stage
スーパーぺこらBONUS
Super Pekora BONUS
Redo
自分の過去に囚われ迷って
Trapped and lost in my own past
そうじゃないよと言い聞かせて全てを自由に
Telling myself "That's not it" and setting everything free
操れるかなんてわからないよと空は霞んで
The sky hazes over as I wonder if I can control it
正解はどこ？
Where is the answer?
僕の手のひらに残る大事なもの
The precious thing remaining in my palm
忘れない記憶
Unforgettable memories
何度でも
Time and again...
君を守り抜くと叫んで
...I shout that I will protect you to the end
巻き戻しの中掴んだ合図を
The signal I grasped while rewinding
離さない...
I won't let go...
散りばめた想い
Scattered feelings
今一度きりの願いへ
Towards a one-time wish
次への僕に
To my future self
託したよ
I entrusted it
いつかの約束
A promise from back then
光の道しるべにある
Becoming a guiding light
誓いを さあ
Now, take the oath
君のため
For your sake
最期まで
Until the very end
涙さえ力に変えて きっと
Transforming even tears into strength, surely
描いていた 望む未来へ
Toward the future I envisioned and desired
繋ぐよ
I'll connect them
想像を超える 事態に狂って
Going mad at a situation beyond imagination
爪を立てて 足掻きもがいて
Digging in my nails, struggling and squirming
心は 人生の過ちを
My heart [repeats] the mistakes of life
繰り返しては 嫌いになって 泣いていても
Repeating them and coming to hate them, even if I'm crying
君の憧れは いつも輝いていた
The thing you yearned for was always shining
I'll be come back
I'll be back
To your future, Go away
僕は 抗うだろう 運命に
I will surely resist destiny
諦めちゃいないから
Because I'm not giving up
結ばれた意志は 独りきりじゃない強さへ
The bound intentions lead to a strength that isn't alone
紡いだ糸を
The spun thread...
手繰り寄せ 見つけた瞳は 理想を現実に変える
...I pull in; the eyes I found change ideals into reality
世界はそう
The world is indeed...
君のため
...for your sake
最初から
From the very start
胸に抱いた思い出と ずっとあの目から続く決意で
With the memories held in my heart and the determination from that day
飛べるよ
I can fly
見て
Look
君が例え 僕のこと 忘れても
Even if you should forget about me
僕はもう忘れない 誰も傷つけず
I won't forget anymore, without hurting anyone
消えそうな過去を 救い出すための時間よ
It's time to rescue the vanishing past
ここから
From here...
始まれ
...let it start
巡りゆく一瞬を 今一度きりの願いへ
The circling moment towards a one-time wish
確かに僕は
Certainly, I...
託されたいつかの約束 光の道しるべになる
...was entrusted with a promise that becomes a guiding light
誓いを さあ
Now, take the oath
君のため
For your sake
最期まで
Until the very end
涙さえ力に変えて きっと描いていた望む未来へ
Transforming even tears into strength, surely toward the envisioned future
繋ぐよ
I'll connect them
7を狙うぺこ！
Aim for the sevens, peko!
PEKO RUSH
スーパーぺこBONUS
SUPER PEKO BONUS
ルミナス
Luminous
伝え合った 心の温度を
The warmth of the hearts we shared
そっと大事そうに 抱え歩いていた
I walked while gently holding it dear
答えのない 願いの中で
Within a wish that has no answer
言葉は未来変えて
Words change the future
幼い頃 ずっと 夢に見ていた 私
The me that I've always dreamed of since I was young
...不安はまだ続くけど
...the anxiety still continues, but
君がいれば
if you're here
少しは強くなれる気がして
I feel like I can become a little stronger
明日の色を重ねた
Layering the colors of tomorrow
呼んだ希望辿って 止めた世界を超えた
Tracing the hope I called for, I crossed the stopped world
諦めない想いいつしか心繋げた
Unyielding feelings eventually connected our hearts
泣いていたって笑って 明日迎えに行こう
Even if we were crying, let's smile and go meet tomorrow
決めた誓い辛くて倒れても
Even if the oath I made is painful and I fall
君のココロを 守るため
To protect your heart
記憶のない時の流れに
In the flow of time without memories
きっと求めていた温かさはあって
The warmth I surely sought was there
包まれた瞬間全ての
In the moment I was enveloped, all of
思いは君へ巡る
My thoughts go out to you
空に向かって走り手にした
Running toward the sky, I took hold of it
いくつもの遠い光胸にしまって
Storing many distant lights in my chest
私の中の輝きに変え
Changing them into a brilliance within me
迷いを全部払ってとぼう
Brushing away all hesitation, let's fly
正解の見えない入り組んだ迷路を抜け
Escaping the intricate maze with no visible answer
君が流した涙で心目覚めた
My heart woke up through the tears you shed
そして知った世界はこんなにもまだ綺麗で
And the world I learned about is still so beautiful
新しい可能性を生むだろう
It will surely give birth to new possibilities
時のカケラの願いから
From the wish of a fragment of time
救い信じては揺れた想い
Believe in salvation, the swaying feelings
私が始まりに立って
As I stand at the beginning
君の笑顔取り戻すよ
I'll take back your smile
真実の奇跡になって
Becoming a true miracle
呼んだ希望辿って 止めた世界を超えた
Tracing the hope I called for, I crossed the stopped world
諦めない想いいつしか心繋げた
Unyielding feelings eventually connected our hearts
泣いていたって笑って 明日迎えに行こう
Even if we were crying, let's smile and go meet tomorrow
決めた誓い辛くて倒れても
Even if the oath I made is painful and I fall
君のココロを 守るため
To protect your heart
君の
I'll stay
側にいよう
by your side
野うさぎタワーをやっつける!
Defeat the Nousagi Tower!
押せ!!
Press!!
必殺
Finishing Move
おらーでぺこー！
Oraa de peko-!
スーパーぺこらBONUS
Super Pekora BONUS
闘いの詩
作詞：三本葎　作曲：THE NEUTRAL
Song of Battle
Lyrics: Sanbon Mugura / Composition: THE NEUTRAL
GET UP GET DOWN 闘いの時
GET UP GET DOWN, time for battle
脆弱な心のままに
Remaining as a fragile heart
GO TO NIGHT NOW すべてかけて
GO TO NIGHT NOW, risking everything
守るべきものがあるはず
There must be something to protect
一人で生きてく そんな言葉に
Living alone, in those words...
隙間を開けている 甘えるこの日々
These pampered days that open up a gap
大切な人たちが うつむいても
Even if the people I cherish look down
気付かぬふりをして 心塞ぐのか
Do I pretend not to notice and close off my heart?
まだやり直せるかな
Can I still start over?
もう一度だけなら
If it's just one more time...
逃げるような生き方は もうやめよう
Let's stop living as if we're running away
GET UP GET UP GET UP 闘いの時
GET UP GET UP GET UP Time to fight
脆弱な心のままに
Just as my fragile heart dictates
GO THROUGH NIGHT ALL すべてかけて
GO THROUGH NIGHT ALL Putting everything on the line
守るべきものがあるはず
There must be something worth protecting
勝利者の足元で 誰かが泣いてる
At the feet of the victor, someone is crying
勝ち負けを避けれない この日々の中で
In these days where winning and losing cannot be avoided
悔しさを陰口で 零していくような
Dropping my frustration through backbiting...
卑怯な奴には もうなりたくない
I don't want to be a coward anymore
まだ間に合うかな
Is it still in time?
きっとここなんだろうな
It must be right here
勝ち負けを越えてでも 今立ち上がれ
Even beyond winning and losing, stand up now
Yeah Yeah Yeah 闘いの時
Yeah Yeah Yeah Time to fight
脆弱な心のままに
Just as my fragile heart dictates
Oh Oh Oh Oh すべてかけて
Oh Oh Oh Oh Putting everything on the line
守るべきものがあるはず
There must be something worth protecting
守るべき人がいるはず
There must be someone worth protecting
yeah yeah yeah yeah 覚悟はいいか 脆弱な心を叩け
Yeah yeah yeah yeah Are you ready? Strike your fragile heart
OH OH OH OH 君は君を かけてでも立ち上がるんだ
Oh oh oh oh Even if you put yourself on the line, stand up
Yeah Yeah Yeah 闘いの時
Yeah Yeah Yeah Time to fight
脆弱な心のままに
Just as my fragile heart dictates
Oh Oh Oh Oh すべてかけて
Oh Oh Oh Oh Putting everything on the line
守るべきものがあるはず
There must be something worth protecting
守るべき君がいるはず
There must be you worth protecting
歌っちゃうのだぺこー！
I'm gonna sing-peko!
絶唱
Crescendo (Zesshou)
スーパーぺこらBONUS
Super Pekora Bonus
Listen to my song...
僕の声は聞こえていますか？ Please tell me
Can you hear my voice? Please tell me
答えのない虚構の空目指し Fly far away
Aiming for the answerless fictional sky, Fly far away
言葉じゃ足りないから 僕のすべて受け止めて
Words are not enough, so please accept everything of me
...できない　したくないよ
...I can't... I don't want to
初めて知る　感覚を
This sensation I'm feeling for the first time
君に歌うよ
I will sing to you
永遠の始まりを
Of the beginning of eternity
だから笑って
So please smile
誰よりも熱く
More passionately than anyone
誰よりも強く
More strongly than anyone
抱きしめるよ
I will hold you tight
震える心
My trembling heart
揺さぶればいい
It's okay to shake it
男 男 男が燃える
Man, man, a man is burning with passion
それが運命（さだめ）よ 男
That is his destiny, a man
槍持て 弓持て 法螺を吹け
Hold the spear, hold the bow, blow the conch shell
行くぞは男の 花舞台
We're going to the man's stage of glory
煮え立せ 唸らせ 大神楽（だいかぐら）
Make it boil, make it roar, the great festival
逝けや松風 修羅を切り拓け
Go, Matsukaze, carve through the carnage
幾千万の 敵陣目掛け 切り込め
Aim for the millions of enemy lines and charge in
崩せ！
Break them!
叩け！
Strike them!
潰せ！
Crush them!
崩せ！
Break them!
叩け！
Strike them!
潰せ！
Crush them!
地獄の馬と 友と駆ける 魔物に候（そうろう）
Galloping with a horse from hell and friends, appearing like a demon
崩せ！
Break them!
叩け！
Strike them!
潰せ！
Crush them!
ゆけ！
Go!
叩け！
Strike them!
潰せ！
Crush them!
待ってみせようぞ 傾奇者（かぶきもの）よ
I'll show you, I'll wait, O Kabukimono
それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそれ よっしゃあ！
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho! All right!
漢
Warrior
男 男 男が惚れる
Man, man, a man is admired
命短し 恋せよ男
Life is short, fall in love, man
男 男 男が燃える
Man, man, a man is burning with passion
それが運命（さだめ）よ 男
That is his destiny, a man
この影とも申すは
The name of this shadow is
茨ヶ谷の鉄兜
The iron helmet of Ibaragaya
前田慶次が馬にて候
Maeda Keiji on horseback
吠えろや 喚（おら）べや 勝鬨（かちどき）を
Roar, shout, raise the victory cry
恵手（めで）には 契りの 男伊達（おとこだて）
In my hand, a man's chivalry pledged
桜のごとくに 散りて夢
Like cherry blossoms, scattering as a dream
死ぬは運命（さだめ）か 命花と散れ
Is death destiny? Let the life-flower scatter
髑髏（どくろ）が笑う 戦場（いくさば）目掛け 切り込め
Aim for the battlefield where the skull laughs, and charge in
砕け！
Break!
叫べ！
Shout!
揺らせ！
Shake!
砕け！
Break!
叫べ！
Shout!
揺らせ！
Shake!
唸り上げろ 我が槍よ 太刀の血が飛ぶ
Let out a roar, my spear, the blood of the sword flies
砕け！
Break!
叫べ！
Shout!
揺らせ！
Shake!
砕け！
Break!
叫べ！
Shout!
揺らせ！
Shake!
花の慶次 いざ傾（かぶ）き舞う
Keiji of Flowers, now Kabuki-dancing
それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそれ よっしゃあ！
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho! All right!
男 男 男が惚れる
Man, man, a man is admired
色香匂えど 散りぬる男
Though the scent is fragrant, a man scatters like blossoms
男 男 男が惚れる
Man, man, a man is admired
散って花咲け 男
Scatter and bloom like flowers, man
男 男 男が惚れる
Man, man, a man is admired
命短し 恋せよ男
Life is short, fall in love, man
男 男 男が燃える
Man, man, a man is burning with passion
それが運命（さだめ）よ 男
That is his destiny, a man
笑（え）みて散りゆけ 男
Smile as you scatter, man
それが運命（さだめ）よ 男
That is his destiny, a man
それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそ それそれそれそれそれ おりゃおりゃおりゃおりゃ よっしゃあ！
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Take that! All right!
兎田ぺこらが開眼で LIVE継続
Usada Pekora awakens, LIVE continues
開眼
Awakening
スーパーぺこらBONUS
Super Pekora BONUS
甲賀忍法帖
Kouga Ninpouchou
下弦の月が　朧に揺れる夜を
A night when the waning moon shimmers in the haze
包む叢雲
Enveloped by a bank of clouds
磔られた　番いひなか
A crucified pair of nestlings
絡める　無常の罠
Entangled in the trap of impermanence
ああ　今も　くすぶる　想い
Ah, if only these smoldering feelings
胸に　しかと　宿らば
Would take firm root within my breast
水の様に優しく
As gentle as water
花の様に劇しく
As fierce as a flower
震える刃で貫いて
Pierce through with a trembling blade
宿命られた涙を
Even if I close my eyes
瞳の奥閉じても
To these fated tears
貴方を
My eyelids
瞼が　憶えているの
Still remember you
兎田ぺこらタイム
Usada Pekora Time
無明の淵で　終焉を待つ私は
In the abyss of ignorance, I am waiting for the end
噎せぶ水子
A sobbing newborn
海に散られた　縋る恋を両手に
My clinging love, scattered into the sea
包んだまま
Still held in both my hands
もはや　抗えない　共に
I can no longer resist
辿る　血塗りの道を
The blood-stained path we walk together
水の様に優しく
As gentle as water
花の様に劇しく
As fierce as a flower
震える刃で貫いて
Pierce through with a trembling blade
宿命られた涙を
Even if I close my eyes
瞳の奥閉じても
To these fated tears
貴方を
My eyelids
瞼が　憶えているの
Still remember you
AZKiタイム
AZKi Time
水の様に優しく
As gentle as water
花の様に劇しく
As fierce as a flower
震える刃で貫いて
Pierce through with a trembling blade
宿命られた涙を
Even if I close my eyes
瞳の奥閉じても
To these fated tears
流れる　血汐を　止められない
I cannot stop this flowing blood
蜜の様に零れて
Spilling like honey
徒の様に散りゆく
Scattering like blossoms
儚い祈りを掻き消して
Drown out my fleeting prayer
宿命られた二人を
Even if the blue-black darkness
葵闇が裂いても
Tears our fated selves apart
貴方と
I will drift
揺蕩う　隠り世まで
With you until the world beyond
スーパーぺこら
BONUS
Super Pekora
You're already dead 'cause I
will never love you now
And maybe when you're going back to home
I'm already gone
Sometimes I think about
when you always stayed in my arms
Please tell me why
I can't love you when I see your face now
何度もいなくなって
I've disappeared time and again,
嘘に代わっていっても
and even as it all turned into lies,
新しい感情には
I'll never end up having
なり果てず
any new feelings.
I'm sorry for you
You're already dead 'cause I
will never love you now
And maybe when you're
going back to home
I'm already gone
今だけじゃなく
Not just for now,
僕だけじゃない
and not just for me.
この世界中の
Nowhere in this whole world
何処にも君を
is there anyone
愛するものはない
who would love you.
いつか届いた君の出した
The promise you once made
約束は果たせず
remained unfulfilled,
僕らはバラバラに
and we were shattered
砕け散った
into pieces.
あの日のふたりのように
If we vanish like we did that day,
同じ気持ちじゃないと
without ever knowing
知らずにいなく
that our feelings
なってしまうのなら
were no longer the same...
You're already dead 'cause I
will never love you now
And maybe when you're
going back to home
I'm already gone
何度目の愛？
How many loves?
何度目の嘘？
How many lies?
この世界中の誰でも
No one in this whole world
僕を愛するべきじゃない
should ever love me.
You're already dead and you
You're already dead and you're
already dead...
You're already dead 'cause I
will never love you now
And maybe when you're
going back to home
I'm already gone
今だけじゃなく
Not just for now,
僕だけじゃない
and not just for me.
この世界中の
Nowhere in this whole world
何処にも君を
is there anyone
愛するものはない
who would love you.
スーパーぺこら
BONUS
Super Pekora
そっと吐き出した溜息を吸い込んだ
I breathed back in the sigh I softly let out.
後悔は苦い味残して
Regret leaves a bitter taste behind.
いつも何で肝心なこと言えないまま
Always unable to say the important things
次の朝が顔を出して
The next morning shows its face
嫌になった運命をナイフで切り刻んでもう一度
Even if I carve up the fate I've come to hate with a knife once more
やり直せたらキミに出会えないかも
If I could start over, I might not meet you
僕の声が響いた瞬間に始まる
It begins the moment my voice resounds
命のリミット
The limit of life
心臓がカウントしてる
My heart is counting down
叶えても
Even if it comes true
終わらない願い
The never-ending wish
汗をかいて
Sweating
走った
and running
世界の
the world's
秒針は
second hand
いつか
will one day
止まった
leave me when I've stopped
僕を置いていく
leaving me behind
あと何回
How many more times
キミと笑えるの？
can I laugh with you?
試してるんだ僕を
Testing myself
Catch the moment
一個、幸せを数えるたびに
Every time I count one piece of happiness
変わっていく未来に怯えてしまうけど
I get scared of the changing future, but
愛情の種を大切に育てよう
Let's carefully nurture the seeds of love
分厚い雲もやがて突き抜けるかな
I wonder if we'll eventually break through the thick clouds
キミの声が響いた僕の全身を通って
Your voice resounded and passed through my whole body
心臓のドアをノックしてる
Knocking on the door of my heart
臆病でも
Even if I'm a coward
開けちゃうんだよ
I'll open it up
信じたいから
Because I want to believe
何もないと思ったはずの足元に
At my feet, where I thought there was nothing
いつか
will one day
深く
deeply
確かな根を生やす
grow certain roots
嵐の夜が来たとしても
Even if a stormy night comes
揺らいだりはしない
I won't waver
何度でも
As many times as it takes
追いついたり追い越したり
Catching up or overtaking
キミが不意に
You suddenly
分からなくなって
became unrecognizable
息をしたタイミングが合うだけで
Just the timing of our breaths matching
嬉しくなったりして
makes me happy
集めた一秒を永遠にしていけたらなあ
If only I could make the seconds I've gathered into an eternity
僕の声が響いた瞬間に始まる
It begins the moment my voice resounds
命のリミット 心臓がカウントしてる
The limit of life, my heart is counting down
叶えても
Even if it comes true
終わらない願い
The never-ending wish
汗をかいて走った
Ran, sweating
世界の秒針が
The second hand of the world
いつか
will one day
止まった僕を置いていく
leave me behind when I've stopped
あと何回キミと笑えるの？
How many more times can I laugh with you?
あと何回？
How many more times?
試してるんだ僕を
Testing myself
Catch the moment
逃さないよ僕は
I won't let it slip away
この瞬間を掴め
Grasp this moment
Catch the moment
予告
Preview
うそだぺこ
It's a lie, peko
次回 集結の園へ
Next time: To the Garden of Gathering
次回、集結の園へ。勝つのは、さあ、どっちだ！？
Next time, to the Garden of Gathering. Which one will win, come on!?
スーパーぺこらBONUS
Super Pekora Bonus
花びら散る
Flower petals fall
...いゆく
...fading away
夢なら 果てなく
If it's a dream, endlessly
それなら 涙は
Then, the tears
どこへと 帰らん
Where will they return?
集結の園へ
Toward the Gathering Garden
作詞：MEGUMI 作曲：たかはしごう
Lyrics: MEGUMI, Composition: Go Takahashi
仕組まれている 集結さえも
Everything is orchestrated, even this gathering
求め過ぎてた答えならば
If it is the answer we have sought too much
記号の中で 泳ぎ疲れて
Tired of swimming within the symbols
行き着く先は ただの仮初め
The destination is just a transient place
長い時 離れても
Even if separated for a long time,
知っている
I know
必ず呼び合う 絆を
The bond that always draws us together
運命と呼ぶ事
Is called 'destiny'
抱いて 抱きしめても抜け出せない
Hold me; even if I embrace you, I can't escape
定められた境から
From the destined boundary
溶けて なくなるほどの進化へと
Towards an evolution that melts and disappears
おかえりなさい
Welcome home
白い結晶が ふりそそぐ都市
In the city where white crystals fall
全ては包まれるだけ
Everything is simply being enveloped
誰が 決めた訳でもない夢を
To the dream that no one ever decided upon
おかえりなさい
Welcome home
心のままに
As your heart desires
君の瞳に 映るその影
The shadow reflected in your eyes
何を思って 何を見てる
What are you thinking? What are you seeing?
感じる事に 信じる事に
About feeling, and about believing,
委ねる事に 臆病になる
And about surrendering, I grow cowardly
長い時 待っていた
I have waited for a long time
微笑んで 支えになりましょう
Let me smile and be your support
一人で 空に願うのなら
If you pray to the sky alone
いつか 繰り返す命の出口
One day, the exit of life that repeats
さらにその先の道も
And the road beyond it
きっと 出会えると信じて泣こう
Believing we'll surely meet, let's weep
おやすみなさい
Good night
赤い血潮が 渦巻く波間
In the waves where red blood swirls
寄せては返す営み
The cycle of ebbing and flowing
愛し 愛され 一つになるまで
Until we love, are loved, and become one
おやすみなさい
Good night
時は満ちるから
For time will be fulfilled
長い時 離れても 知っている
Even if separated for a long time, I know
必ず呼び合う 絆を
The bond that always draws us together
運命と呼ぶ事
Is called 'destiny'
抱いて 抱きしめても抜け出せない
Hold me; even if I embrace you, I can't escape
定められた境から
From the destined boundary
溶けて なくなるほどの進化へと
Towards an evolution that melts and disappears
おかえりなさい
Welcome home
白い結晶が ふりそそぐ都市
In the city where white crystals fall
全ては包まれるだけ
Everything is simply being enveloped
誰が 決めた訳でもない夢を
To the dream that no one ever decided upon
おかえりなさい
Welcome home
心のままに
As your heart desires
望むままに
As you wish
心のままに
As your heart desires
いやーこれ、当たりがずっと続いてるぺこなー。
Wow, the winnings just keep coming, peko!
ということで...
And so...
そんな皆さん、どーもぺこです。
Hello everyone, it's Pekora!
今年もあます、兎田ぺこら誕生日記念2025のグッズ紹介、イェーイ！
It's that time again, the introduction of Usada Pekora's Birthday Celebration 2025 merchandise, yay!
ということで、一つ目はこちら！
So, the first item is this!
Tシャツ！
A T-shirt!
おなじみの悠木はぐれ先生に描いてもらったぺこなんですけども...
It's illustrated by the familiar Yuuki Hagure-sensei...
いつもとはちょっと違ったカッコいいぺこらのデザインぺこ。
It features a cool Pekora design that's a bit different from usual, peko.
ぜひともね、これを着てたくさんお出かけして行ってくれたら嬉しいぺこ。
I'd be happy if you wore this and went out often, peko.
二つ目はこちら！
The second item is this!
ランダムじゃらじゃらアクリルキーホルダー！
Random Jingle-Jangle Acrylic Keyholders!
スロットの絵柄にちなんだぺこだを、まええり先生に描いてもらったぺこ。
These feature Pekoda based on slot machine icons, illustrated by Maeri-sensei, peko.
可愛くないぺこですか？
Aren't they cute, peko?
ぜひともね、あのスロットの絵柄ぺこなんで、同じ絵柄を三つ揃えて、ジャックポット狙ってみてほしいぺこ。
Since they're slot patterns, I'd love for you to get three of the same and aim for the jackpot, peko.
三つ目はこちら！
The third item is this!
ぺこ推しバッグ！最近ね、ちょっと痛バを作ってくれてる人をよく見かけるぺこなので...
The Peko-Oshi Bag! Lately, I've been seeing many people making "ita-bags," so...
野うさぎのために、ぺこらバージョンも作ってみたぺこ。
I made a Pekora version for the Nousagi, peko.
たくさんね、なんかもうじゃらじゃらじゃらじゃらつけて、ライブだったりとかイベントとかに持っていってほしいぺこです。
I want you to put a ton of stuff on it and bring it to concerts or events, peko.
そして、四つ目はこちら！
And the fourth item is this!
どんちゃんカードホルダー！
Don-chan Card Holder!
さっきのカバンに付けてもよし、チェキカードを入れるもよし、もう何でもカード入れてくれ！
You can put it on the bag I just showed, or put your cheki cards in it, just put any card you want!
ということで、こちらフルセット購入特典で、チェキ風ブロマイド。
And here is the full set purchase bonus, a cheki-style bromide.
さっきのカードホルダーにも入れるべき！もう入れてください、ぺこ。ぜひともね。
You should definitely put this in the card holder! Please do, peko. Really.
今回も直筆サインを頑張るぺこですので、ぜひともね、皆さんお手に取っていただけたら嬉しいぺこです。
I'll be working hard on the handwritten signatures again this time, so I'd be very happy if everyone could get one, peko.
そしてそして、なんと！ホロライブカード特典もあるみたいぺこです。
And also, wow! It seems there's a Hololive card bonus too, peko.
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として、去年から発売されたホロライブオフィシャルカードゲームで使用できるカードが一枚付いてくるぺこ。
As a bonus for the full set, you'll get one card for the Hololive Official Card Game that was released last year, peko.
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象ぺこですので、ご注意ください。
Please note the card is only for those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop, peko.
いやーこの後もね、名曲があるんで、それもお楽しみに。
Wow, there are still some great songs coming up, so look forward to those.
というか、あれ、グッズ紹介結構長いことやったはずぺこなんだけど、当たり全然、え、来てなくないぺこか？これやばくないぺこか？
Wait, I thought I'd been doing the merch introduction for a long time, but there haven't been any winnings, eh, at all, peko? Isn't this bad, peko?
終わっちゃわないぺこか？やばいやばいやばい。
Is it going to end, peko? Oh no, oh no.
え、終わった？
Wait, is it over?
まだ野うさぎたちと、ジャガブシを見ていないぺこ！
I haven't seen the performance with the Nousagi yet, peko!
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ マモー
Mimo Mimo Mimo Mimo Mimo Mamo
サガリズ サガリズ ゴーゴー ビゴー
Sagarisu Sagarisu Go go Vigo
早く君と踊りたいから
I want to dance with you soon
今夜も楽しみ ワクワク・ベイビー
I'm excited for tonight too, Waku-waku Baby
長い髪を振り乱してる
Waving my long hair around
負けちゃいそうだよ パラパラ・ダンシング
I feel like I'm going to lose, Para-para Dancing
隙がなくても変身するさ
I'll transform even if there's no opening
狼男は ラブリー ワン・ワン
The werewolf is a lovely woof-woof
振って振って腰々振って
Shake it, shake it, shake those hips
ハートがノったら コネクリ・ポーション
When your heart is in it, Konekuri Potion
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ マモー
Mimo Mimo Mimo Mimo Mimo Mamo
サガリズ サガリズ ゴーゴー ビゴー
Sagarisu Sagarisu Go go Vigo
振れてない 立ってない
Not swaying, not standing
リッチな遊びさ バブ・バブ・バブリー
Rich play, bub-bub-bubbly
フェロモン 足りなきゃ
If you lack pheromones
ビーツで 陶酔
Intoxicated by the beats
真っ赤っか 甘い吐息
Deep red, sweet sighs
揺れるハートに飛び込んで
Jump into the swaying heart
行くとこまで行って おかえりハッピー
Go all the way, welcome back happy
熱い眼差し落として
Cast a hot gaze
優しく口づけ ドキッドキッ
A gentle kiss, doki-doki
切なくなるほどカワイイ
So cute it makes me ache
壁紙にさせてくれたらラッキー
Lucky if you let me be your wallpaper
オールの最後は昇天
At the end of the all-nighter, we ascend
向こうの世界で パヤッパヤッ
In the world beyond, paya-paya
Good night ベイビー Sexy レディ
Good night Baby, Sexy Lady
今宵はノリノリ
Tonight is groovin'
Moonlight ベイビー Cutie レディ
Moonlight Baby, Cutie Lady
朝までバリバリ
All out until morning
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ
Meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo
パラミズ ザラミズ ゴザザザ ビボ
Paramisu zaramisu gazazaza bibo
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ
Meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo
パラミズ ザラミズ ゴザザザ ビボ
Paramisu zaramisu gazazaza bibo
汗が光る 色っぽいよね つま先立ちで見つめるバービー
Sweat shines, you're sexy, right? Watching Barbie on tiptoes
ところ狭しと ステップ踏めば 素敵な体が揺れるよ ヘイヘイ
Stepping everywhere in this tight space, your lovely body sways, hey hey
意味深な視線 誘ってくるね 負けちゃいられない にらめっこアップップ
Suggestive glances, inviting me. I won't lose this staring contest, puff!
ジョーダンだぜ 分からせるから 一緒に夜明けを見ようよ レディ ヘイ
Just kidding, I'll show you. Let's watch the dawn together, Lady. Hey!
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ
Meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo
パラミズ ザラミズ ゴザザザ ビボ
Paramisu zaramisu gazazaza bibo
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ
Meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo
パラミズ ザラミズ ゴザザザ ビボ
Paramisu zaramisu gazazaza bibo
しゃしゃじゃない やるじゃない 気を抜きゃたちまち おねだり放題
Not just pushy, doing well. If I slip up, you'll be asking for everything
お仕置きするなら まずは景気づけ シャンパン あ！それ！いき！
If it's punishment, first some champagne to celebrate. Ah! That! Go!
眩しいくらい 華やいで 飲み込まれそうに 輝くレディ
So bright it's dazzling, so glamorous. A shining lady like she'd swallow me up
ハーレムナイト 叶えたい たまには寄り取り緑飛び
Harem night, want to make it come true. Once in a while, pick and choose
これでもホントは 素直さ 真面目で誠実 売り込みたいね
I'm actually honest. Serious and sincere, I want to sell myself
マメな男は モテるはず そんな下心 見え見え
Diligent men should be popular. That ulterior motive is plain to see
Dancing Baby Stepping Lady
踊るよビキビキ
Dancing, biki-biki
Tiny Baby Honey Lady
脱いだらバリバリ
Once stripped, bari-bari
落としたつもりが スルリと 腕をすり抜ける
Thought I caught you, but you slip right through my arms
ふわりと漂う 魔法の言葉で
Floating softly with magical words
イチゴロ ニコロ サンコロ モンサイ...
Ichigoro nikoro sankoro monsai...
ずっとそばにいてほしいの 妙にイ慣れたセリフもちょっと
I want you to stay by my side forever. Even those practiced lines a bit...
惑わされてもいいほどに 君に夢中だよ ときめき
Enough that I don't mind being deceived, I'm crazy about you. Excitement!
揺れる心に 飛び込んで 行くトコまで行って おかえりハッピー
Jump into my swaying heart. Go as far as you can, then welcome back happy
熱いまなざしで 落として 優しい口づけ ドキドキ
Drop me with a hot gaze. A gentle kiss, heart pounding
切なくなるほど カワイイ 髪なびかせてくれたらラッキー
So cute it's painful. I'm lucky if you let your hair flutter
オールの最後は 昇天 向こうの世界で パヤッパパヤ
Ascension at the end of the night. In the world beyond, payappa-paya
Good Night Baby Sexy Lady
今宵はノリノリ
Tonight we're having fun
Moon Light Baby Cutie Lady
朝までバリバリ
All out until morning
ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ ミーモ
Meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo meemoo
コンプリート機能作動中
本日のライブは終了いたしました
Complete function in operation
Today's live has ended.
神オブ神
God of Gods